fspilotshop.com 2009-06-19

# FlightSim Pilot Shop - Flight Simulation Hardware, Software and Accessories

> This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for the Flightsim.com Pilot Shop. eDimensional, Inc. and Flightsim.com, Inc. take our clients privacy and security very seriously. 
> 
> ## Information Collection and Use
> 
> eDimensional, Inc. is the sole owners of the information collected on this site. WE DO NOT SHARE, RENT, SELL OR OTHERWISE DISCLOSE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION AT ANY TIME, FOR ANY REASON.
> 
> ## Newsletter
> 
> If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. This information is never shared with any third parties and the user can unsubscribe at any time.
> 
> ## Order
> 
> We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill a customer order. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.
> 
> ## Security
> 
> This website takes every precaution to protect our user information. We use the highest level of 128-bit encryption on our site during the entire checkout process. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just surfing. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. No employee at any time will ever see your credit card information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to support@eDimensional.com.
> 
> ## Links
> 
> This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that eDimensional, Inc. and Flightsim.com, Inc. are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.
